rightnow.com 2003-04-11

# Privacy Statement | RightNow Technologies

|    
---|---|---  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
| 

> ## Privacy Statement
> 
> RightNow Technologies, Inc. is committed to your right to privacy. As a visitor to our website or user of our product, you deserve the ability to control the uses of your personal information. This privacy statement discloses our privacy practices.
> 
> This Privacy Statement is directed at visitors to our website. We have adopted a separate Statement called "Privacy when Hosting" to address the privacy needs of our customers whose software we host (see <http://www.rightnow.com/privacy/hosting.php>, etc.).
> 
> RightNow agrees to notify you of the following:
> 
>   1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personal identification is collected from you through the website
>   2. The organization collecting the information
>   3. How the information is used
>   4. With whom the information may be shared
>   5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
>   6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under RightNow's control
>   7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
> 

> 
> **If you feel that RightNow is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact us by addressing your concerns to[cpo@rightnow.com](mailto:cpo@rightnow.com).**
> 
> RightNow collects information from our users at several different points on our website to enable us to better inform you about our product. By knowing your preferences we can deliver relevant information that meets your needs and ensure that your visit to our site is quick, easy and productive. RightNow is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.
> 
> ### Registration
> 
> In order to use some functions on this website, a user must first complete a registration form. During registration, the user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. RightNow does not share any personally identifiable or private customer information submitted online with third parties. Demographic information may also be requested (such as zip code or type of business). This information may be stored, analyzed and used to assist us to improve our services. 
> 
> ### Cookies
> 
> RNT uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to simplify and enhance the experience on our site (i.e. prefilling forms similar to those you may have already completed). Once the user closes their browser, the cookie information is no longer available through our server. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether to accept it. If a user rejects the cookie, they can still use our site. 
> 
> ### Log Files
> 
> We use IP addresses in log files to analyze trends, administer the site, track a user's movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Log files do not enable us to access personally identifying information, such as email addresses. 
> 
> ### Links
> 
> This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that RightNow is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected at this website. 
> 
> ### RightNow eService Center Support Site
> 
> Currently, RightNow eService Center support is available in its entirety to RightNow customers whose eService Center license agreement is current. If you are a current RightNow eService Center customer, you may receive web support by visiting our support site and logging in. This allows you to to view our published Answers and ask questions of our support personnel. Your questions and our answers may be published on our website, and made available to other website visitors. However, those visitors will have no way of knowing that one or more of the questions on the website was asked by you. 
> 
> ### Webcasts
> 
> RightNow offers its users an opportunity to participate in live Webcasts which are hosted by PlaceWare, Inc. A participant must register through a link to take part in the Webcast. The information collected at the time of registration (such as name, address, e-mail address) enables us to contact the participant with password and login information for the Webcast. Additionally, registrants may be contacted by phone to ensure that they have the needed information for attending the Webcast. The participant is given an opportunity to opt-in to receive future e-mails about eService education, products and events either by phone or via on-line surveys. A user may opt-out of being contacted in the future by emailing [info@rightnow.com](mailto:info@rightnow.com) with their request to delete them from the "Webcast email list." Please refer to placeware.com for more information regarding their privacy statement. 
> 
> ### Newsletter
> 
> If a user wishes to subscribe to our _eService OnTarget_ newsletter, they must opt in. At that point we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter can unsubscribe when they receive it by clicking on a link at the bottom of the newsletter. The user will then be given an opportunity to opt in or out of future newsletters and opt in or out of further periodic RightNow communications. 
> 
> Email forwarding functionality is provided in the newsletter. Using this functionality will forward the newsletter privately. However, if you use other forwarding methods, like those provided in your email client, they may transfer personally identifiable information.
> 
> ### Public Forums
> 
> This site makes chat rooms forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 
> 
> ### Surveys
> 
> From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 
> 
> ### Children
> 
> RightNow products are for use by businesses. Therefore, we would not expect children under the age of 18 to provide us with any personally identifiable information. 
> 
> ### Hot Connections Referral Program
> 
> If a customer joins our Inner Circle Program and decides to refer a prospect as a part of that program, we ask them to provide the prospect's name, company, title, phone, address (if available), as well as information about their relationship with the prospect. The Inner Circle member can request a call from the sales representative prior to the prospect being contacted. The referral prospect may contact RightNow at [info@rightnow.com](mailto:info@rightnow.com) to request the removal of this information from the RightNow database. 
> 
> ### Security
> 
> RightNow takes precautions to protect our customers' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line using standard security best practices such as firewalls, encryption and intrusion detection. Full backups are performed every week on the entire file system and incremental backups are done daily. Finally, all hosted servers are kept physically secure in world-class hosting data centers. 
> 
> ### Credit Cards
> 
> We do not currently accept credit card information on-line. If and when credit card information is requested in the future, this policy will be updated. 
> 
> ### Special Offers
> 
> We send all new Inner Circle members a welcoming email to verify password and username. We send the _e-Service OnTarget_ newsletter to those people who specifically request it. Visitors to our website will occasionally receive information on products, services and special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see "Opting Out" below 
> 
> ### Updating Personal Information and Opting Out:
> 
> We encourage our users to update our record of any personal information which changes (such as your zip code). Information can be corrected/updated on any registration form. Users can also opt out of our services by emailing a request to info@rightnow.com. Inner Circle information may be updated online at <http://www.rightnow.com/customers/inner.html>. 
> 
> ### Changes to Privacy Policy
> 
> RightNow will update this policy from time to time. A "last revised" date will always be included on the bottom of the statement. To keep up-to-date with RightNow's' policy, please check this page periodically. 
> 
> ### Contacting the Website
> 
> If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, you can contact us on [cpo@rightnow.com](mailto:cpo@rightnow.com). 

| 

RightNow eService Center has given us the power to get closer to our employees and provide the specific, focused type of information they need, when they need it. It's also given our service representatives a powerful tool that not only helps but also teaches. It's knocked down our internal learning curve substantially.  

McKesson Chemical

A Tangle of Information - Simplified!  
  
---|---
